[{"command":["/start"],"question":[],"routing":[{"input_data":["ANYTHING"],"response":[{"response_text":"Say friend and enter!","buttons_type":"ReplyKeyboardMarkup","buttons":["friend","enemy"]}],"next_question":"enter-riddle","validataion":""}],"data_container":["text"],"validation":"","answer_error":"","next_question_onerror":""},{"command":[],"question":["enter-riddle"],"routing":[{"input_data":["friend"],"response":[{"response_text":"WELCOME TO THE MORIA!\nEnter the mine?","buttons_type":"ReplyKeyboardMarkup","buttons":["/yes","/no","superultralongstringtotype"]}],"next_question":"enter-the-mine?","validataion":""},{"input_data":["ANYTHING"],"response":[{"response_text":"Think a little more, friend.."}],"next_question":"enter-riddle","validataion":""}],"data_container":["text"],"validation":"","answer_error":"","next_question_onerror":""},{"command":[],"question":["enter-the-mine?"],"routing":[{"input_data":["/yes","yes","да","/ok","/okey"],"response":[{"response_text":"Gates about to fall!!"},{"response_text":"*Actions:*\n/runIntoTheMines\n/smokeApipe\n/whatTimeItIs"}],"next_question":"entered-the-mine","validataion":""},{"input_data":["/no","no","нет"],"response":[{"response_text":"You will go back at this moment!!?"}],"next_question":"entered-the-mine-rejected","validataion":""}],"data_container":["text"],"validation":"","answer_error":"","next_question_onerror":""},{"command":[],"question":["entered-the-mine"],"routing":[{"input_data":["/runIntoTheMines"],"response":[{"response_text":"So dark around here... Can't see anything.. but you are alive!"}],"next_question":"","validataion":""},{"input_data":["/smokeApipe"],"response":[{"response_text":"*RIP*\nYou are dead under the rocks."}],"next_question":"","validataion":""},{"input_data":["/whatTimeItIs"],"response":[{"response_text":"<?php return \"MSK time is *\".date(\"Y-m-d H:i:s\").\"*\";"},{"response_text":"But this can't help you"}],"next_question":"entered-the-mine","validataion":""},{"input_data":["ANITHING"],"response":[{"response_text":"You are dead under the rocks.\n(any)"}],"next_question":"","validataion":""}],"data_container":["text"],"validation":"","answer_error":"","next_question_onerror":""},{"command":[],"question":["entered-the-mine-rejected"],"routing":[{"input_data":["ANITHING"],"response":[{"response_text":"Well, i can see, that you are stupid enough, but you can't go back now. So *ENTER THE F@#%EN MINE!*\n/okey :("}],"next_question":"enter-the-mine?","validataion":""}],"data_container":["text"],"validation":"","answer_error":"","next_question_onerror":""}]